Papers of Morris K. Udall, 1920-1995
University of Arizona Library Special Collections
- Legislative Files, 1961-1990
  - Committee Files, 1961-1992
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 4140 Nuclear Regulatory Commission; HR 4689, Nuclear Waste Negotiator-Energy and Environment Markup, Udall Notebook. 1987-1989 (Box 317, Folder 17)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Arizona/Florida Land Exchange Act-Phoenix Indian School, Udall Correspondence, Statements, Memos, Bills,and Reports. 1987-1989 (Box 317, Folder 18-20)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 4519, Arizona/Florida Land Exchange Act, Clippings. 1987-1989 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 4519, Clippings. 1987-1989 (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 5232, Southwest Low Level Radioactive Waste Compact-Floor Action. 1987-1989 (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Udall Notebooks. 1987-1989 (Box 318, Folder 4-5)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee Hearings (Volumes 1-3). 1987-1989 (Box 318)
    - Post Office and Civil Service: Miscellaneous. 1987-1989 (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Board Radioactive Waste Management. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Budget Fiscal Year 1991-Full Committee Markup, Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Bureau of Indian Affairs Budget. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Conference on Budget Reconciliation. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Defense Nuclear Facilities Safety Board Budget. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Department of Energy Budget Fiscal Year 1990-Hearing, Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Department of Energy (DOE) Budgets. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Waste Disposal Contracts (DOE). 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 8)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Recommendations. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 9)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Decommissioning Nuclear Plants. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 10)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Denver Radium Waste Disposal. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 11)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Environmental Restoration and Waste Management-Five-Year Plan. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 12)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, EPA Uranium rule. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 13)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Hazardous Waste Court Cases. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 14)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Nuclear Power Hearings. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 15)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Japan Nuclear Waste Disposal-Ishibashi Visit. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 16)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Memos to Members. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 17)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Nuclear Issues. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 18)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Nuclear Non-Proliferation. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 19)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Nuclear Plant Licensing Reform. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 20)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Notices for Hearings. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 21)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Radiation Hazards. 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 22)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Hearing on Shoreham. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, U.S. Navy Nuclear Propulsion Program-Nuclear Waste Disposal. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Global Warming, Reference Material. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 3-4)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Global Warming, Udall and Myers Correspondence. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Hot Dry Rock 50 Megawatt Electrical Generation Project. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Legislative Priorities. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Staff Memos to Udall. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Subcommittee on Mining & Natural Resources, Mining. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 9)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Monitored Retrievable Storage Review Commission. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 10-11)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, National Energy Strategy. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 12)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Bills. May 1989 (Box 320, Folder 13-14)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 1549, Nuclear Regulatory Commission Authorization Fiscal Year 1990-1991. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 15)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Hearing,Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 16)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Full Committee Markup, Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 320, Folder 17)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Regulatory Commission Budgets. 1985-1990 (Box 320, Folder 18)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Regulatory Commission, The Fortuna Affair. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: The Roger Fortuna Affair, Actions of Nuclear Regulatory Commission Officials. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Issues (Roger Fortuna Case). 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 3-4)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Regulatory Commission, Nuclear Licensing Issues. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Regulatory Commission User Fees. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Office of the U.S. Nuclear Waste Negotiator. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Oil Crisis. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 8)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Phoenix Indian School. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 9)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Press Releases. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 10)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Rules Committee. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 11)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Swedish & French Nuclear Facilities Inspection Tour, Itinerary Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 12)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Swedish & French Nuclear Facilities Inspection Tour, Correspondence & Memos. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 13)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Swedish & French Nuclear Facilities Inspection Tour, Reference Material. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 14)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Texas Low Level Radioactive Waste Disposal Authority-Legislative Briefing, Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 15)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Tumamoc Hill. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 16)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: U.S. Nuclear Waste Technical Review Board. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 17)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Yucca Mountain Waste Disposal Site. 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 18)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 402, Amend Mineral Leasing Act of 1920. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 706 & 3285, Nuclear Safety Board. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 765, Commission/National Policy/Cleanup DOE Facilities. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 780 & S 11, California Desert Protection Act. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 4)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, HR 1102, Amend the Price Anderson Provisions of the Atomic energy Act of 1954-Contractors. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, HR 1102-Hearing. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR1549, Nuclear Regulatory Commission Authorization Act Fiscal Year 1990-1991-General. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR1549, Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 8)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR1549, Energy and Environment Markup-Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 9)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR1549, User Fees. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 10)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2480, Uranium Enrichment Bills. 1989-1990 (Box 322, Folder 11)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2480, Uranium Enrichment Bills. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR2480, Uranium Enrichment Bills-Louisiana Energy Services. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Hr 2480, Uranium Enrichment. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2642, Southeast Low Level Radioactive Compact- Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2642, Management Compact Amendments Consent Act of 1989. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR2642, Joint Hearing-Energy and Environment Markup-Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2783, Uranium Enrichment Bill Amendments and Bill. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2783, Correspondence. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 8)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2783, Memos. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 9)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2783, Nuclear Regulatory Commission & EPA Proposals. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 10)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2783, Nuclear Pharmacy. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 11)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2783, Nuclear Waste. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 12)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 2783, Reference. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 13)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 4140, Nuclear Regulatory Commission Reorganization. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 14)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Agenda. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 15)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Administrative Speeches. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 16)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Atomic Energy Act of 1954, Section 221C. 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 17)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management, Reorganization. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Civilian Radioactive Waste Management Program. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Nuclear Regulatory Commission and DOE Budgets Fiscal Year 1991. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Hearing on "The Role of Nuclear Energy in U.S." 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Hearing on Licensing Uranium Enrichment Plants-Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Energy. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Smith Barney Report July1980-Udall Notebook. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Memos to Members. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Hearing on the Future of Nuclear Power-Udall Notebook. May 1990 (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Waste Isolation Pilot Plant-Udall Notebook. May 8, 1990 (Box 324, Folder 10)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Kerr McGee vs. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 11)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Medicine. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 12)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Regulatory Commission Appeal Board. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 13)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Nuclear Regulatory Commission Waste Confidence Decision. 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 14)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Mill Tailings (Uranium/Thorium). 1989-1990 (Box 324, Folder 15)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 5505, Amend Atomic Energy Act of 1954-Low Level Radioactive Waste, General. 1989-1990 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: HR 5505, Reference Material & Hearings. 1989-1990 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Staff Memos to the Nuclear Regulatory Commission. 1989-1990 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs: Neumont Mining. 1989-1990 (Box 326, Folder 2-3)
  - Chairman's Special Project Files, 1974-1990
    Arranged alphabetically by subject heading, then chronologically. Morris K. Udall served as Chairman of the Interior and Insular Affair Committees from 1977-1991. The Chairman's Special Project Files contain correspondence, memos, briefings, books, notes, and printed material relating to a wide range of issues that hold a particular interest and importance for Mr. Udall. These include the Alaska Lands Act, coal slurry pipelines, nuclear issues, strip mining and wilderness. Of particular interest are the files relating to the Interior Committee investigation of the Three Mile Island Nuclear Accident. Also included in this subseries are the files of Henry Myers, Science Advisor to the Interior committee and Mark Trautwein, Interior Committee staffer who served as a point man on wilderness issues.
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Admiralty Island. 1977-1978 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Alaska Officials, Reports and Testimony. 1977-1978 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Alaskan Public Opinion Research. 1977-1978 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Background Materials. 1977-1978 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Bill Drafts. 1977-1978 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Bills. 1977-1978 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Clippings. 1977-1978 (Box 327, Folder 7)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Committee Prints. 1977-1978 (Box 327, Folder 8)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Dangerous River Bridge Issue. 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Debate. 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Hearings & Testimony, Civil Address-Secretary of Interior. 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: General. 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 4-8)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Merchant Marine & Fisheries. 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 9)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Printed. 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 10-11)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Witness Lists. 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 12)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Interior Department Amendments. 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 13)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Issues Analysis. 1977-1978 (Box 328, Folder 14)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Markup. 1977-1978 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Alaska Native Claims Settlement Act, Background. 1977-1978 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Native Selection Process. 1977-1978 (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Native Subsistence Provisions. 1977-1978 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Oil Industry. 1977-1978 (Box 329, Folder 5)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Office Technology Assessment Study, Minerals. 1977-1978 (Box 329, Folder 6)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Other Bills. 1977-1978 (Box 329, Folder 7)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Reports and Summaries. 1977-1978 (Box 329, Folder 8)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Section Analysis. 1977-1980 (Box 329, Folder 9)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Senate Markup. 1977-1980 (Box 329, Folder 10)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Subcommittee on General Oversight. 1977-1980 (Box 329, Folder 11)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall Correspondence. 1977-1980 (Box 329, Folder 12-13)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall Markup Notebook. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall Memos and Reports. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall Notebook on D-2 Proposal. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Other Udall Bills. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall and Other Bills, Section Drafts/Notes. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: U.S. Borax Proposed Mine. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Wildlife Issues. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 7)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Ad Hoc Compromise. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 8)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Administrative Amendments. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 9)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Administration Lockup. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 10)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Alaska Coalition. 1977-1980 (Box 330, Folder 11)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Amendments. 1979-1980 (Box 331, Folder 1-2)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Arctic Game Range. 1979-1980 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Bills. 1979-1980 (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Comparisons of Bills HR 39,S 222 and S 9. 1979-1980 (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Co-sponsors. 1979-1980 (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Eagle Study. 1979-1980 (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Senator Gravel, Press Releases and Mailings. 1979-1980 (Box 331, Folder 8)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Hearing. 1979 (Box 331, Folder 9)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Huckaby Substitute. (Box 331, Folder 10-11)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Jurisdiction Issues. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Oversize Maps. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Markup Strategy. 1979 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Mineral Exploration Coalition. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Mud Bay Watershed, Logging. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: National Park,Wilderness Data. (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Native Americans, Court Cases. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Political Strategy Sessions. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 8)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Politics. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 9)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Post House Vote, Miscellaneous. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 10)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Press Releases. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 11)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Senate Amendments. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 12)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Sports Hunting Packet. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 13)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: States Rights. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 14)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Staff Briefings. 1979-1980 (Box 332, Folder 15)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Statistics. 1979-1980 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall-Anderson. 1979-1980 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall Correspondence. 1979-1980 (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall Correspondence, Native Americans. 1979-1980 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall Notes for Rules. 1979-1980 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall Notes. 1979-1980 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Alaska Lands Act, HR 39: Udall Statements and Articles. 1979-1980 (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Correspondence. 1975-1976 (Box 334, Folder 1-2)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: Energy and Environment Subcommittee, General. 1975-1976 (Box 334, Folder 3-5)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: Testimony, Environmental Impact Statement, Task Report. 1975-1976 (Box 334, Folder 6-8)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 2330, Conference Committee Meetings. 1975-1976 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 2330, Nuclear Regulatory Commission Authorization Bill. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 2330, Administration Position. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: Correspondence, Con. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: Correspondence, Pro. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Udall Statement. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Bill Drafts. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Comparison of House/Senate Versions. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Interior Committee. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Technology. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 9)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Clippings. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 10)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Notes. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 11)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Udall Statements. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 12)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Bills and Analysis. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 13)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 4230, Public Works. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 14)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Udall Working File. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 15)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Amendment, Mineral Leasing Act of 1920. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 16)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Amendments. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 17)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Commodities Clause-Analysis. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 18)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Public Works & Transportation Committee. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 19)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Texas Eastern Amendments. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 20)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Imports. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 21)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Interior Committee Amendments. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 22)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Miscellaneous. 1981-1984 (Box 335, Folder 23)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Agricultural Issues. 1983-1984 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Railroads. 1983-1984 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Railroad Labor Issues. 1983-1984 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-National Coal Association Policy Issues Book. 1983-1984 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Conference. 1983-1984 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Reference Material. 1983-1984 (Box 336, Folder 6-8)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Energy and Environment Subcommittee, Background Notebook. 1983-1984 (Box 336, Folder 9-10)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Waste Water. 1983-1984 (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 1010, Coal Pipeline Act of 1983-Water Issues. 1983-1984 (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 3857, Coal Slurry Pipeline Act of 1983. 1983-1990 (Box 337, Folder 1-2)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 3857, Reports. 1983-1990 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline: HR 3857, Amendment Mineral Leasing Act of 1920. 1983-1990 (Box 337, Folder 4)